hey guys this looks like a fun one we
have three of these nine to the X Powers
so I'm going to write that as 3 times 9
to the X power next I want to get rid of
this three so I'm going to divide both
sides by 3. these two threes cancel
leaving us with just nine to the X power
on the right hand side we have a 139
threes being multiplied by each other on
top and we have a single three on bottom
one of these 139 threes up here is going
to cancel with this 3 down here so we
only have 138 threes being multiplied
which is 3 to the 138 power so this 9 to
the X power we can rewrite the 9 as 3
squared and that'll still be to the X
power this is going to be equal to 3 to
the 2x power you can just multiply the
two powers and then we'll just bring
down the right hand side so we have 3 to
the 2x is equal to 3 to the 138 since
the bases match the only way these two
sides could be equal to each other is if
the exponents are equal to each other
and that gives us 2x is equal to 138
after we divide both sides by 2 we get X
is equal to 69 nice and let's put a box
around that how exciting